{
    "subject": "resource/Umayyad_Caliphate",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Damascus",
    "human_readable": "Damascus is the capital of the Umayyad Caliphate.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9834166765213013,
            "question": "Was Damascus a significant city during the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9713038206100464,
            "question": "Why was Damascus chosen as the capital of the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.951155960559845,
            "question": "Where was Damascus located during the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.947117269039154,
            "question": "How long was Damascus the capital of the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.922931969165802,
            "question": "What other cities served as capitals for the Umayyad Caliphate besides Damascus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9153818488121033,
            "question": "What was the capital of the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.905746579170227,
            "question": "How did the Umayyad Caliphate's presence in Damascus impact the city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8549458980560303,
            "question": "Who were some notable rulers of the Umayyad Caliphate based in Damascus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8391939401626587,
            "question": "What role did Damascus play in the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8383781313896179,
            "question": "Are there any historical records about life in Damascus during the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Damascus is the capital of the Umayyad Caliphate.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8943_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did Damascus play in the Umayyad Caliphate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8943_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some notable rulers of the Umayyad Caliphate based in Damascus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8943_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the Umayyad Caliphate's presence in Damascus impact the city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8943_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8943_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8943_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8943_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8943_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8943_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8943_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8943_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8943_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8943_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8943_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The Umayyads were mentioned as the rulers of the Islamic Caliphate with Damascus as their capital, and one document even specified that Damascus was established as the capital after moving it from Madinah."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Damascus was the capital of the Umayyad Caliphate,\" which directly supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}